// An array that holds all the questions and possible answers, as well as indicating the correct answer.
const allQuestionsA = [
    {
        question: 'Who is the current all-time NBA leading points scorer?',
        answers: ['Michael Jordan', 'LeBron James', 'Kobe Bryant', 'Karl Malone', 1],
    },
    {
        question: 'Which NFL team does quarter-back Patrick Mahones play for?',
        answers: ['Buffalo Bills', 'Philadelphia Eagles', 'Kansas City Chiefs', 'Miami Dolphins', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which Hockey team has won the most stanley cup trophies?',
        answers: ['Montreal Canadiens', 'Toronto Maple Leafs', 'New York Rangers', 'Boston Bruins', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has won the most mens singles tennis titles?',
        answers: ['Bjorn Borg', 'Pete Sampras', 'Roger Federer', 'Novak Djokovic', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which country won the mens FIFA World Cup in 2018?',
        answers: ['Germany', 'Brazil', 'France', 'Argentina', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which golfer currently holds the record for most major wins?',
        answers: ['Jack Nicklaus', 'Tiger Woods', 'Ben Hogan', 'Arnold Palmer', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which football team has won the most Champions Leauge trophies?',
        answers: ['AC Milan', 'Real Madrid', 'Bayern Munich', 'Manchester United', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the only athlete to win olympic gold medals in the 100m & 400m?',
        answers: ['Carl Lewis', 'Usain Bolt', 'Michael Johnson', 'Yohan Blake', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which nation has won the most rugby union world cups?',
        answers: ['England', 'New Zealand', 'France', 'South Africa', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which footballer is the current all time Premier Leauge top goal scorer?',
        answers: ['Wayne Rooney', 'Harry Kane', 'Alan Shearer', 'Sergio Aguero', 2]
    },
];
const allQuestionsB = [
    {
        question: 'In darts, what is the highest score of a single dart?',
        answers: ['40', '60', '100', '80', 1],
    },
    {
        question: 'Who has the current most F1 race wins?',
        answers: ['Max Verstappen', 'Sebastien Vettel', 'Lewis Hamilton', 'Michael Schumacher', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which boxer did Muhammad Ali fight in "The rumble in the jungle?"',
        answers: ['George Forman', 'Joe Frazier', 'Sonny Liston', 'Larry Holmes', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which French city is famous for its 24hr motor race?',
        answers: ['Paris', 'Marseille', 'Lille', 'Le Mans', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Jessica  Enniss-Hill competed for Great Britain in which sport?',
        answers: ['Heptathlon', 'Long Jump', 'Triathlon', 'Pole Vault', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which nation won the 2019 cricket world cup?',
        answers: ['Australia', 'England', 'India', 'Sri Lanka', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'The Chicago Cubs & Boston Red Sox play which sport?',
        answers: ['Baseball', 'Ice Hockey', 'American Football', 'Basketball', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which footballer has scored the most goals in world cup history?',
        answers: ['Lionel Messi', 'Cristiano Ronaldo', 'Miroslav Klose', 'Diego Maradona', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which female tennis player has won the most grand slam titles?',
        answers: ['Serena Williams', 'Stefi Graf', 'Billie Jean King', 'Margaret Court', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which MLS franchise team does David Beckham own?',
        answers: ['LA Galaxy', 'Seattle Sounders', 'Inter Miami', 'Portland Timbers', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which nation call their rugby team the Springboks?',
        answers: ['Australia', 'South Africa', 'Fiji', 'Samoa', 1]
    },
];
const allQuestionsC = [
    {
        question: 'The Ryder Cup is related to which sport?',
        answers: ['Cricket', 'Badminton', 'Golf', 'Football', 2],
    },
    {
        question: 'How many players are there on each team in a game of basketball?',
        answers: ['8', '5', '7', '6', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which basketball team did Michael Jordan spend most of his career playing for?',
        answers: ['New York Knicks', 'Washington Wizards', 'Chicago Bulls', 'Detroit Pistons', 2]
    },
    {
        question: 'David Beckham played his last professional football game for which club?',
        answers: ['Paris St Germain', 'Manchester United', 'La Galaxy', 'AC Milan', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which sport takes place in a velodrome?',
        answers: ['Hockey', 'Cycling', 'Swimming', 'Gymnastics', 1]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which city did the first modern summer olympic games take place in 1896?',
        answers: ['Rome', 'Paris', 'London', 'Athens', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which country won the first FIFA World Cup in 1930?',
        answers: ['Uruguay', 'Brazil', 'France', 'Germany', 0]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which female tennis player has won the most grand slam titles?',
        answers: ['Serena Williams', 'Stefi Graf', 'Billie Jean King', 'Margaret Court', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'Which sport is Ronnie Osullivan associated with?',
        answers: ['Golf', 'Cricket', 'Darts', 'Snooker', 3]
    },
    {
        question: 'What is the term for a score of 1 over par on a golf hole?',
        answers: ['Eagle', 'Bogey', 'Foul', 'Birdie', 1]
    },
];